JASON PAINTER: Hi, I'm Jason.
Today, we're painting on glass.
We have put the first coat, the liner, and the fill in on all three of the steps.
It's looking like it's ready now to be--we can really start touching up the liner.
We can really start touching up the black.
If we look at it, we can see spots that-that filled in and spots that didn't, and we don't have to worry about how these thick line--it really looks bad right now, but we're just in the beginning stages.
So, really, those we want to do is make sure that all of the black lines connect, everywhere that we know they're going to need to, and all of the lines are filled in that we know we're going to need to.
So, we just take the angle brush back again, get black back out, and really, the less paint you have on here, the better, just a very little on the tip of your brush.
This line right here needs to be filled in, and we're not actually going to make any brush strokes.
We're just going to set the paint right on it.
Fill that in, just like that.
We don't have to do anything anymore.
We'll be defeating the purpose.
We'll just spread that paint out thinner and thinner, and just be frustrated in the end.
So, this line here is not touching.
We can just put a little dab of black there, same as up here.
Just, basically, just want everything to touch and that's going to make a big difference when we fill in with the white.
So, go ahead and fill in everywhere that you gotta fill in, and look at it, and we'll wait for that to dry.
And touch up the white.